A Guide to the Virginia Intercollegiate Association Papers 1954-1969
Johnston Memorial Library, Virginia State University
- Administrative Correspondence
  - Subject Schools Correspondence
    - Washington, B.T. High School - Norfolk 1954-1958 (Box-folder 43:1)
    - Washington, B.T. High School- Norfolk 1959-1962 (Box-folder 43:2)
    - Washington, B.T. High School- Norfolk 1962-1963 (Box-folder 43:3)
    - Washington, B.T. High School- Roanoke 1958-1963 (Box-folder 43:4)
    - Washington, B.T. High School- Staunton 1954-1957 (Box-folder 43:5)
    - Washington, B.T. High School- Staunton 1960-1963 (Box-folder 43:6)
    - Washington, B.T. High School- Suffolk 1954-1959 (Box-folder 43:7)
    - Washington, B.T. High School- Suffolk 1960-1962 (Box-folder 43:8)
    - Washington, B.T. High School- Suffolk 1963-1969 (Box-folder 43:9)
    - Watkins, G.W. High School 1954-1967 (Box-folder 43:10)
    - Watson High School 1954 (Box-folder 43:11)
    - Watson High School 1960-1963 (Box-folder 43:12)
    - Westside High School 1954-1957 (Box-folder 43:13)
    - Westside High School 1961-1964 (Box-folder 43:14)
    - Williams, Johnson High School 1954-1958 (Box-folder 43:15)
    - Woodson, Carter High School (Dinwiddie) 1954-1957 (Box-folder 43:16)
    - Woodson, Carter G High School- Dinwiddie 1966-1967 (Box-folder 43:17)
    - Woodson, Carter High School-Hopewell 1954 (Box-folder 43:18)
    - Wright, A.T. High School 1954-1956, 1957-1959 (Box-folder 43:19)
    - Wright, J.J. High School 1954-1957 (Box-folder 43:20)
    - Wright, John J. High School 1964-1967 (Box-folder 43:21)
    - Wyatt, Edward High School 1954-1957 (Box-folder 43:22)
    - Wythe, George Jr. High School 1966-1967 (Box-folder 43:23)
    - Awards-Track (Box-folder 44:1)
    - Baseball-Group I, Championship 1958 (Box-folder 44:2)
    - Baseball 1960 (Box-folder 44:3)
    - Baseball Group I 1960 (Box-folder 44:4)
    - Baseball Group II 1960 (Box-folder 44:5)
    - Baseball 1963 (Box-folder 44:6)
    - Baseball 1966 (Box-folder 44:7)
    - Baseball (Box-folder 44:8)
    - Baseball (Box-folder 44:9)
    - Baseball (Box-folder 44:10)
    - Baseball (Box-folder 44:11)
    - Basketball Tournament 1954-1955 (Box-folder 44:12)
    - Basketball Tournament 1954-1955 (Box-folder 44:13)
    - Basketball 1963 (Box-folder 44:14)
    - Basketball Photo-Dunbar 1966 (Box-folder 44:15)
    - Basketball Tournament Game 1966 (Box-folder 44:16)
    - All Tournament Team Group I (Box-folder 44:17)
    - Basketball Group I, Championship 1967 (Box-folder 44:18)
    - Basketball Photo-Armstrong 1967 (Box-folder 44:19)
    - Basketball 1968 (Box-folder 44:20)
    - Basketball 1968 (Box-folder 44:21)
    - Basketball 1968 (Box-folder 44:22)
    - Basketball 1968 (Box-folder 44:23)
    - Basketball 1968 (Box-folder 44:24)
    - Basketball Tournament (Box-folder 44:25)
    - Basketball Tournament (Box-folder 44:26)
    - Basketball Tournament-Group I (Box-folder 44:27)
    - Basketball Tournament-Group II (Box-folder 44:28)
    - Basketball (Box-folder 44:29)
    - Basketball Group I (Box-folder 44:30)
    - Basketball Tournament (Box-folder 44:31)
    - Basketball Tournament (Box-folder 44:32)
    - Basketball Tournament (Box-folder 44:33)
    - Basketball Group II- Runner ups (Box-folder 44:34)
    - Coaches Meeting (Box-folder 45:1)
    - Commissioner-Fields (Box-folder 45:2)
    - Drama (Box-folder 45:3)
    - Drama Festival (Box-folder 45:4)
    - Drama-Peabody High School (Box-folder 45:5)
    - Executive Committee (Box-folder 45:6)
    - Football Clinic 1960 (Box-folder 45:7)
    - Football Culpepper (Box-folder 45:8)
    - Girls Athletic Association 1966 (Box-folder 45:9)
    - Meeting (Box-folder 45:10)
    - Music Festival (Box-folder 45:11)
    - Choir Festival (Box-folder 45:12)
    - Music (Allstate) (Box-folder 45:13)
    - Music (Allstate) (Box-folder 45:14)
    - National Honor Society 1968-1969 (Box-folder 45:15)
    - Photos- W.K. (Box-folder 45:16)
    - Photo's 1958-1959 (Box-folder 45:17)
    - Photo's 1958-1959 (Box-folder 45:18)
    - Photo's- Miscellaneous (Box-folder 45:19)
    - Student Participation Association 1957 (Box-folder 45:20)
    - Student Participation Association 1959 (Box-folder 45:21)
    - Student Participation Association 1966 (Box-folder 45:22)
    - Student Participation Association Conference (Box-folder 45:23)
    - Tennis 1960 (Box-folder 45:24)
    - Tennis 1961 (Box-folder 45:25)
    - Tennis 1963-1964 (Box-folder 45:26)
    - Tennis (Box-folder 45:27)
    - Tennis (Box-folder 45:28)
    - Tennis (Box-folder 45:29)
    - Track 1960 (Box-folder 45:30)
    - Track Championship 1960-1961 (Box-folder 45:31)
    - Track 1960-1961 (Box-folder 45:32)
    - Track 1960 (Box-folder 45:33)
    - Track 1960-1961 (Box-folder 45:34)
    - Track 1961 (Box-folder 45:35)
    - Track Championship Team (Box-folder 45:36)
    - Track 1963-1964 (Box-folder 45:37)
    - Track (Box-folder 45:38)
    - Track (Box-folder 45:39)
    - Track 1965 (Box-folder 45:40)
    - This box contains the official programs for the V.I.A. state basketball Tournament from 1967-1969. It has the V.I.A. calendar of events from 1965-1969. It includes playbills for the Annual drama festival from 1955-1968. Administrative forms and certificates honoring V.I.A. participants. (Box-folder 46:1)
    - This box includes 11 picture blocks. Many of the pictures are of basketball teams receiving awards after games. The others are of other people of groups receiving awards. (Box-folder 47:1)
    - This box contains the master basketball schedules and football schedules from 1957 to 1968. There are also envelopes including the V.I.A- general season tickets. Golf, Tournament scores, V.I.A. football schedules, and Basketball Schedule. (Box-folder 48:1)
    - Artafacts (Box-folder 49:1)
    - Artafacts (Box-folder 50:1)
    - Artafacts (Box-folder 51:1)
    - Scrapbooks (Box-folder 52:1)
    - Scrapbooks (Box-folder 53:1)